## about

I am a digital designer and web developer with a solid background in digital marketing. I have worked on the design and developement of multiple websites and web applications. While pivoting to a fulltime developer career, I am interested in growing and expanding my knowledge of software engineering fundamentals. My aim is to join a large company and learn while applying my talents for practical outcomes.

# experience

#### Freelance

2020 - Present

## Web developer

Fullstack Development:

- Design of a digital educational web application
- Database design
- RoR stack
- Front end development with Boostrap framework

Web content Publisher:

- CMS management
- Digital design

## Digital360

2018 - 2019

## **Digital Marketing Publisher and Designer**

Marketing Development:

- Graphic Design for digital marketing
- Publishing and website management for SEO purposes

Website Development:

- Wireframing and sketch designs for front end dev
- Webflow design and build
- CMS implementation and maintenance

# **FLAMINKO Playing Cards**

2017 - Present

#### Designer & Founder

Designer:

- Built front end for Flaminko website
- Designed over 7 playing card decks and tuck boxes
- Created assests for digital marketing

SM Campaign Manager:

- Conducted market research and analysis
- Planned Marketing campaign and targets
- Released and grew instagram, twitter and facebook platforms

Achievements:

- Succesfully Funded 3 Kickstarters

# education

### 2020 - Le Wagon

Web Development Course - March Certificate Awarded

# 2017 - RMIT University

**Bachelor of Information Technology** (Games & Graphics Programming)

- December Degree Awarded

## 2014 - Yokohama International School

International Baccalaureate

- May Session Diploma Awarded

# extra-curricular

### **High School Student Council**

- Council Member Sophomore and Junior year
- Student Council President Senior Year Melbourne University Fencing Club
- Treasurer

#### **Fencing Victoria**

- Australia Uni games Second place (Men's Ind Epee 2015)
- VIC Men's Team Foil First Place (2016)
- NATIONALS Men's Team Epee First Place (2019)

# skill set



















